# **JOHNNY DUNN**

https://aithub.com/iddunn/ https://iddunn.aithub.io/portfolio/

Summary

Full-stack dev experienced in building machine learning infrastructure and data analytics pipelines, and training and deploying models. Also experienced in web3 / smart contract development, as well as game development and AR / VR with Unity.

### Professional Experience

Tilting Point New York, NY

Senior Blockchain Engineer

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

- Acted as blockchain architect and engineer building out infrastructure for full end-to-end NFT and token integrations (ERC-20
  / ERC-1155) in mobile games publishing SDK, supported on multiple blockchains including IMX, Solana, Polygon.
- Development of smart contracts, and help overseeing development of cryptocurrency wallet widgets and payments.

eBay New York, NY

Software Engineer 2 (Full-Stack)

June 2020 - April 2021

- Improved UX serving ads; extended REST APIs in Scala & Spring-Boot to service data to UI and ML models asynchronously.
- Worked on scraping dashboard functionality to verify data integrity across services.
- Created deployment infrastructure process enabling rapid frontend development cycles for backend and ML team. Set up
  Jenkins pipelines to connect underlying UI libraries, server-side rendering backends for web, and ML APIs returning ads data.

### Freelance (Grapple Media, Notebrush, Edelman, HAL)

Remote

NLP Engineer / Software Engineer / Product Designer (Contract)

- November 2018 May 2021
- Created user stories, animated wireframes and functional product demo for Notebrush's MVP.
- Developed web crawling infrastructure with automated pipeline to feed data into training models for Grapple Media. Trained sentiment analysis models for text analysis for news articles.
- Trained deep learning models to create photographic filters applying artistic aesthetics of specific movies to selfies for one of Edelman's interactive AI exhibits.
- Developed / sold sentiment analysis model and infrastructure to HAL (HereAfterLegacy), and continued dev work for a year.

IPSoft New York, NY

Cognitive Implementation Engineer

June 2017 - December 2017

- Implemented modules for virtual assistant Al Amelia for corporate client-facing solutions following agile practices, working with APIs / tools provided by R&D.
- Improved workflow and productivity by writing data processing scripts to be distributed to internal teams.

## Projects

 Hype..blog - The future of digital newsrooms powered by Al and human staff, using LLMs and Stable Diffusion 2023 <a href="https://github.com/jddunn/restless">https://github.com/jddunn/restless</a>

Restless - Always-on anti-malware software using malicious language processing (HAN model) techniques
 https://github.com/jddunn/restless

Text-RPG-Engine - ES6 JS library to create text adventures / interactive fiction with custom player interactions 2020
 https://aithub.com/iddunn/text-rpg-engine

### Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Design and Technology (May 2017) – Parsons School of Design

#### Awards

5<sup>th</sup> Place, AT&T National VR and AR Challenge, with THiNKIMMERSIVE team. (http://npe100.com/)

2017

XRC Labs Young Entrepreneurs Residential Program

Spring 2017

### Skills

<b>Programming Languages</b>	Solidity   Python   Golang   JavaScript   Java   Scala   C#   SQL   HTML   CSS
Frontend	React   Next.js   Redux / Redux Toolkit (RTK)   Electron   Bootstrap   ChakraUl   MaterialUl   NextUl   Tailwind   D3.js   three.js
Backend	FastAPI   Django   Keras   TensorFlow   OpenCV   spaCy   NLTK   NumPy   SciPy   pandas   scikit-learn   PyTorch   Celery   BS4   Selenium   Scrapy   ethers.js   web3.js   LangChain   OpenAl
Databases	MySQL   PostgreSQL   SQLAlchemy   Pinecone DB   Elasticsearch   Hadoop   MongoDB   Redis
DevOps	AWS (EC2, Elastic Beanstalk, Amplify, RedShift)   Docker   Kubernetes   Jenkins
Tools / Software / Other	Unity   Git   Postman   Linux   Burp Suite   Adobe Creative Suite   Processing   openFrameworks   SketchUp   PyCharm   IntelliJ   Visual Studio   PyCharm